Love knows no limit.
Until Forever is a drama, romance film directed by Michael Linn.
Until Forever: The Michael Boyum Story is a powerful, true account of one young
man's courageous battle with leukemia and his journey of faith.
Michael Boyum, played by Stephen Anthony Bailey.
Michelle Larson, played by Madison Lawlor.
Matthew Boyum, played by Jamie Anderson.
James Boyum, played by Hayden Loven.
Mr. Fenton, played by James Stephens III.
Bonnie Boyum, played by Susan Chambers.
Until Forever is a 2016 American independent biographical romantic drama film written and
directed by Michael Linn and starring Stephen Anthony Bailey and Madison Lawlor.
It is based on the life of Michael Boyum (1976-1999), a 22-year-old man from Inver Grove Heights, Minnesota
who married his high school sweetheart, Michelle Larson, six weeks before he died of leukemia.
The film explores themes of based on true story, leukemia, romance, cancer.
The tone is emotional.